http://www.ultimatejujitsu.com/privacy-policy

Our Privacy Policy
Below we have set out our privacy policy on any information and/or data collected from yourself.
What Information Do We Collect?
Ultimate Ju-Jitsu will collect your email address if you sign up to our discussion forum, sign our guestbook, upload pictures, and/or add an event or club.
Use Of Cookies
If you are a memeber of our forum, we will store a cookie containing your username to be able to log you in automatically to the forum upon your return.
How Do We Use Your Information?
We may periodically send out email notifications (if you have signed up to one of our services mentioned above) to the address you supply with regards to the site as whole, or to specific forum topics you wish to sign up to for updates.
When Do We Share Information?
We do not sell or pass on your personal information to any third party.
How Can I Change The Personal Information Ultimate Ju-Jitsu Holds About Me?
You can edit your profile in the forum section (for forum members) or tell us to modify or delete it via email for anything else that may contain personally identifiable information.
How Do We Protect Your Personal Information?
We are serious about guarding the security of your personal information and the details of any actions performed on our site. We take appropriate organisational and technical security measures to protect your data against unauthorised disclosure and/or processing. We use a secure server to store the information you give us when you register for any of our services, or sign our guestbook.
